imagine you're creating a retail app that sells
electronics you'll first create a list view that
shows all the products and then a detailed view
that shows more information about each product
there's a one-to-one relationship between
each product in the list view that shows
the name image and price and the detailed view
of the product where you show more information
such as multiple images description
manufacturer dimensions weight and so on
in a relational database you might have a table
called products and each row in the table would
contain enough information to populate the
list view then you'll have another table called
product details that contains more information
used to populate the detailed view in redis
similar to a relational database you can create a
collection called products and another collection
called product details here i've imported the
redisome library and i'm modeling the products
collection with fields like name image
and price meant for the product list view
i also have a product details collection
with product id description manufacturer
dimensions weight and a list of images
with redis ohm we can index it like this
and here's how you can query the list view lastly
here's how you query the detailed view but you can
improve this by simply embedding the product
details within the products collection then
when you query you only query for the fields you
need for a particular view this way you can easily
keep all your data in one place this is called the
embedded pattern here are the new models using the
embedded pattern here's how we can index it and
here's how we can query the list view note that
we're returning three fields name image and price
lastly here's how we can query the detail view
looking at our database in redis insight what
you get when you use the embedded pattern
is all of your data in one place so we have our
details embedded within the product collection
you